Ryusuke Lavalla

Full Stack Web Developer

Brooklyn, NY 11237 (917) 741-1730 ryusukelavalla@gmail.com https://linkedin.com/in/ryusukelavalla http://ryusukelavalla.com

Objective

Full stack developer with a passion for applying the most innovative web development technologies to the latest challenges in business. Adaptive to the rapidly unfolding world of digital information.

Expertise - AJAX, Single Page Application, MVC, RESTful API, Responsive Design, SEO

Technical Skills

- Languages: JavaScript, Python, HTML, CSS, JSON, Sass, Bash, SQL, NoSql
- Frameworks/Libraries: Angular.js, Django, JQuery, Node.js, Express.js
- *Operating Software:* Linux (Ubuntu)
- *Tools:* Terminal, Vim, Sublime Text

Professional Experience

Building custom content management systems from the portfolio level to the organizational level using open source technology stacks.

Freelance Full Stack Web Developer

October 2016 - Present http://wolfgangdouglas.com

- Wolfgang Douglas, Brooklyn, NY
 - Digital portfolio using Angular.js, Django, Apache and Postgres; deployed on Amazon Web Services.
 - Created RESTful API endpoints using Django Rest Framework to service single page application.
 - Youtube content integration.
 - Email routing and handling.
 - Support and maintenance.

Freelance Full Stack Web Developer

May 2016 - Present http://rockwallstudios.nyc

Rockwall Studios, Queens, NY

- Worked with designer to deliver responsive studio rental site.
- Brought designs wireframes mockups and PSD's into html and css.
- Built custom CMS to manage content, blog, active floor plan, and SEO using django.
- Deployed on Amazon Web Services with ec2 and s3.
- Instagram content integration via Instagram API and Angular.js.
- Maintain consistent communication with designer to adapt to client's changing needs.

Past Work

Research Assistant, IR Japan, New York, NY Production Assistant, TK Digital, Brooklyn, NY

January 2013 - March 2014 July 2012 - October 2012

Education

General Assembly, New York, NY Marymount Manhattan College, New York, NY Full Stack Web Development Immersive, 2015 BA, Communication Arts, 2012